prefixmag.com 2012-05-23

# Privacy Policy | Prefix

**Last Updated May 7, 2012**

Your privacy is important to us. Accordingly, we have created this Privacy Policy, which explains how and why we collect personal data from you and the ways in which that data is or may be used. 

By visiting Prefixmag.com (“Prefixmag.com Website”), you accept the terms described in this Privacy Policy. Because these rules may be modified from time to time, we encourage you to check this page periodically for updates. 

**Collection of Personal Data**

When you register as a Member of the Prefixmag.com Website, or request information, we will use our online forms to collect personal information such as your name and e-mail address. In addition, if you e-mail us or contact us by some other form of communication, we may collect whatever data you voluntarily provide us at that time. 

**Use of Personal Data**

We may use your personal data in the following ways: 

  1. 1\. For the purpose for which you provided your personal datavv (e.g., for purposes of enrollment or to respond to an inquiry); 
  2. 2\. To send you updates about features and services available as part of the Prefixmag.com Website that we think might be of interest to you. If you do not want to receive these updates, then do not sign up for Prefixmag.com’s mailing list or register as a Member of the Prefixmag.com Website. 

**Collection of Anonymous Data**

The site’s advertisers may engage in the collection of non-personally identifiable information about end users by third parties through the use of cookies and pixel tags 

End users to opt out of behavioral targeting through the opt-out link located at [Opt out](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp). 

Prefix Magazine is participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance's (DAA) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. [Ad Choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). 

Most pages on the Prefixmag.com Website do not require you to provide personal data. When visiting a page, however, you may automatically provide Prefixmag.com with anonymous data that is not linked to your personal data, such as your browser type, Internet Protocol (IP) address, domain name, operating system, access times, and the addresses of referring web sites. 

Cookies. A "cookie" is a string of information that is sent by a website and stored on your hard drive or temporarily in your computer's memory. We use cookies to improve the speed with which you are able to navigate the Prefixmag.com Website, to collect information about your use of the site, and to enable you to use certain on-line features. Although you can disable cookies from your web browser, doing so will prevent you from taking advantage of some security features and customization on the Prefixmag.com Website. 

**Use of Anonymous Data**

We use a service provider to track and analyze anonymous data for purposes of generating statistics regarding the use of the Prefixmag.com Website. We do not link this anonymous data with your personal data. 

**Disclosure of Personal and/or Anonymous Data**

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to prevent fraud, comply with legal process, satisfy any applicable law, regulation or governmental request, or ensure the security of the Prefixmag.com Website or other services. 

**Security**

In order to keep your personal data secure, we restrict unauthorized access through protective technologies, procedures and policies. 

**Links to Third Party Websites**

The Prefixmag.com Website contains links to certain third-party websites. This Privacy Policy governs only those websites owned and maintained by Prefixmag.com. Accordingly, be sure to review the privacy policies that govern your use of other websites.
